Call us today  [(800) 452-6700](tel:8004526700 "call us (800) 452-6700")

[×](javascript:void(0))

* [The #1 Party Entertainment Services Trusted by Major Corporations. Book and Save Now. It’s that easy!](https://charactersforhire.com/)

Privacy Policy
==============

### **Privacy Policy**

**Revised: March 6, 2024**

Your information privacy is important to us. We provide this Privacy Policy to explain how we collect, use, protect, and disclose information and data when you use the website on which this policy is posted (“**_Site_**”) and related services offered through the Site (“**_Services_**”). This Privacy Policy applies to all users of the Site and Services.

This Privacy Policy is specific to this Site—it does not apply to any of our other websites or other online or offline services provided by us.

BY USING THE SITE OR SERVICES, YOU ARE CONSENTING TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY. PLEASE READ IT CAREFULLY.

1. **Personal Information We Collect**

We may collect the following categories and types of “**_Personal Information_**”:

* **Contact Information**: your first and last name, mailing address, email address, and phone number;
* **Other identifying information**: IP address, social media usernames, passwords and other security information for authentication and access;
* **Financial Information**: credit card, debit card and bank account information;
* **Demographic information**: gender, age, employment information and salary information;
* **Geolocation data**;
* **Internet or other electronic activity**: your browsing, search, and click history, including information about how you navigate within our Site and Services and which elements of our Site and Services you use the most;
* **Commercial information**: products or services purchased or viewed on our Site;
* **Audio and visual information**: your videos and photos; and
* **Inferences drawn from the categories described above** in order to create a profile about you to reflect your preferences, characteristics, behavior and attitude.

2. **How We Use Personal Information**

We may use your Personal Information for the following categories of use:

* **Transactional Purposes:** We may use your contact information, financial information, and commercial information to:
    * Receive, process, confirm, send and track your order, subscription or registration;
    * Communicate with you about your order, subscription or registration; and
    * Process any subscription or registration you make to one of our Services.
* **Analytical Purposes**: We may use your other identifying information, internet activity and browsing history, commercial information, demographic information, and geolocation data to analyze preferences, trends and statistics.
* **Marketing and Promotional Purposes**: We may use your contact information, commercial information, demographic information, internet or other electronic activity, geolocation data and inferences to:
    * Inform you of our new products, services and offers;
    * Provide you with targeted advertising;
    * Run contests, promotions and sweepstakes,
    * Provide you with our loyalty program including earning points and awarding and redeeming certificates; and
    * Provide you with other information from and about us, including personalized marketing communications.
* **Maintenance and Improvement of the Site and Services**: We may use your contact information, commercial information, and internet activity and browsing history to:
    * Provide you with the Site and Services, including to send you alerts about your account;
    * Handle your customer services requests; and
    * Help us diagnose technical and service problems and administer our stores, the Site, and the Services.
* **Review and content creation purposes**: We may use your contact information, commercial information, and audio and visual information to enable reviews of our products and to display content that you have created and allowed us to display on our Site and Services and on social media.
* **Security and Fraud Prevention:** We may use your contact information, other identifying information, commercial information, internet activity and browsing history, and inferences to protect the Site and services, our company, and others and to prevent fraud, theft and misconduct.
* **Legal and Other Requirements:** We may use your personal information to comply with legal requirements or when necessary to provide to our lawyers, accountants or other advisors. We may also use your personal information for other purposes for which you have consented to. This may include for a secondary purpose that is related to a purpose for which we collected it, and for which you would reasonably expect us to use your information for.

3. **Sources of Personal Information**

We may collect Personal Information from the following sources:

* **We collect information directly from you**. We may collect contact, demographic and financial information directly from you including when you fill out a form on our Site, sign up for communications from us, or ask us to contact you. The information that we collect depends on the nature of your interactions with us.
* **We collect information from our Service Providers**. We collect information from our Service Providers (defined below) that collect certain Personal Information from or about you on our behalf, such as an analytics software or platform that we use to measure and analyze traffic to the Site, the Services or interaction with our ads. For example, our Service Providers may capture certain usage data to provide and analyze a “session replay” of your activities on the Site, which allows us to optimize the Site and the Services. The session replay may record, for example, clicks, mouse movements, scrolling, typing, navigation through the Site and the technical specifications of your device.
* **We collect information from other third-party sources.** We may also collect information about you from third-party sources, including any information you make publicly available on social media platforms or other online or offline resources, or when you give us consent to link your account to a third-party service or provider.
* **We collect information from you passively**. We may collect internet or other electronic activity passively using tools like browser cookies. This activity is further described in the Cookies and Advertising and Online Tracking sections below.

4. **Categories of Third Parties We Share Personal Information With**

_Service Providers_

From time to time, we may establish a business relationship with other businesses whom we believe trustworthy and who have confirmed that their privacy practices are consistent with ours (“**_Service Providers_**”). For example, we may contract with Service Providers to provide certain services, such as hosting and maintenance, data storage and management, and marketing and promotions. We only provide our Service Providers with the information necessary for them to perform these services on our behalf. Each Service Provider must agree to use reasonable security procedures and practices, appropriate to the nature of the information involved, in order to protect your Personal Information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. Service Providers are prohibited from using Personal Information other than as specified by us.

_Our Affiliates_

We may share Personal Information with businesses controlling, controlled by, or under common control with us, where such affiliates or subsidiaries are acting as our Service Provider, or where required by law.

_Corporate Transactions_

If we merge, are acquired, or are sold, or in the event of a transfer of some or all of our assets, we may disclose or transfer Personal Information in connection with such transaction.

_Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement_

We cooperate with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We may disclose Personal Information and any other information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties if, in our discretion, we believe it is necessary or appropriate in order to respond to legal requests (including court orders and subpoenas), to protect the safety, property, or rights of our company or of any third party, to prevent or stop any illegal, unethical, or legally actionable activity, or to comply with the law.

5. **Privacy Notice Specific to Mobile Messaging**

We will only use information you provide when opting into mobile messaging (the “Program”) to transmit your mobile messages and respond to you, if necessary. **WE DO NOT SELL, RENT, LOAN, TRADE, LEASE OR OTHERWISE TRANSFER ANY PHONE NUMBERS OR CUSTOMER INFORMATION COLLECTED THROUGH THE PROGRAM TO ANY THIRD PARTY FOR SUCH THIRD PARTY’S MARKETING PURPOSES OR OTHERWISE FOR SUCH THIRD PARTY’S OWN BENEFIT**. Nonetheless, we reserve the right at all times to disclose any information as necessary to satisfy any law, regulation or governmental request, to avoid liability, or to protect our rights or property. This Section is strictly limited to the Program and has no effect on other provisions of this Privacy Policy that may govern the relationship between you and us in other contexts. To view our complete Mobile Messaging Terms and Conditions, please see the Terms of Use on our Site.

6. **Cookies**

We may use cookies (a small text file placed on your computer to identify your computer and web browser) and may use anonymous identifiers (a random string of characters that is used for the same purposes as a cookie). We may use cookies and other similar technologies to analyze use of and improve the Site and Services and as described in the Advertising and Online Tracking Section of this Privacy Policy. Most web browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent, however, certain features of the Site or Services may not work if you delete or disable cookies. Some of our Service Providers (defined below) may use their own cookies, anonymous identifiers, or other tracking technology in connection with the services they perform on our behalf.

We may use Google Analytics on the Site and Services to analyze how users use the Site and Services, and to provide advertisements to you on other websites. For more information about how to opt out of having your information used by Google Analytics, visit [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).

7. **Session Replay Technology**

We use session replay technology on our Site. Session replay technology, also referred to as session playback or user experience (UX) replay, collects information regarding records and tracks your interactions with a website or application. It then transforms those logged user events (such as mouse movements, clicks, page visits, scrolling, tapping, etc.) into a reproduction of what you actually did on the website or application. We use session replays for quality control, customer service, fraud prevention and security, and marketing purposes. Our session replay technology is owned and operated by a third-party who acts as our service provider. The information collected by this technology may be collected by, transferred to, and stored by our third-party service provider.

8. **ChatBot Technology**

We use chatbots to help provide customer service and support, including through the use of a virtual assistant. A chatbot is a software application that mimics human conversations in text or voice interactions on our website or through our customer service hotline. It enables the communication between a human and a machine, which can take the form of messages or voice commands. The chatbot is designed to work without the assistance of a human operator. It responds to questions posed to it in natural language as if it were a real person using a combination of pre-programmed scripts and machine learning algorithms. When asked a question, the chatbot will answer using the knowledge database that is currently available to it. If the conversation introduces a concept it isn’t programmed to understand; it will pass it to a human operator. If you use our chatbot service, we will collect any information you provide to us. We will also create and store a transcript of your chat interaction with us which will be shared with and stored by our third-party service provider. We use these transcripts and the information you provide for quality control, customer service, fraud prevention and security.

9. **Advertising and Online Tracking**

We may place advertisements and allow third-party companies to serve ads and collect certain information when you visit the Site. These companies may use certain information (e.g. click stream information, web browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this Site and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of interest to you (i.e., for cross-contextual behavioral advertising). These companies may also collect information about your activities on our Site on your current device and combine it with information about your activities on other websites, mobile apps, and devices. These companies typically collect such information using server logs, cookies, web beacons, tags, pixels, mobile advertising IDs (such as Facebook cookies or Google’s Advertising ID), cross-device linking, and similar technologies. They may match your browsers or devices if you log into the same online service on multiple devices or if your devices share similar attributes that support an inference that they are used by the same person or household. This means that information about your activity on websites or apps on your current browser or device may be combined and used with information collected from your other browsers or devices. These third party partners use this information for our and their own advertising, analytics, attribution, and reporting purposes. Our systems do not recognize browser “Do Not Track” signals, but several of our Service Providers who utilize these cookies on this Site enable you to opt out of targeted advertising practices. To learn more about these advertising practices or to opt out of this type of advertising, you can visit [www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/) or [www.aboutads.info/choices/](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/). Options you make are device specific.

10. **Managing Your Information Preferences**

You can opt out of receiving marketing e-mails from us by following the link provided at the bottom of all marketing e-mails you receive from us. You are able to opt out of receiving marketing e-mails from us, however, you cannot opt out of receiving all e-mails from us, such as e-mails about the status of your account.

11. **Be Careful When You Share Information with Others**

Please be aware that whenever you share information on any public area of the Site or Services, that information may be accessed by others. In addition, please remember that when you share information in any other communications with third parties, that information may be passed along or made public by others. This means that anyone with access to such information can potentially use it for any purpose, including sending unsolicited communications. We cannot control and are not responsible for what such third parties may do with your information, so you should exercise caution when choosing to share it.

12. **Security**

We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to help protect the confidentiality and security of information transmitted to us. Personal information may be accessed by persons within our organization, or other entities described in this Privacy Policy, or our third-party service providers, who require such access to carry out the purposes described in this Privacy Policy, or as otherwise permitted or required by applicable law.

However, no data transmission over the Internet or other network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure, and no security measures can provide absolute protection. As a result, while we strive to protect information transmitted on or through the Site or Services, we cannot and do not guarantee the security of any information you transmit on or through the Site or Services, or that you otherwise provide to us, and you do so at your own risk.

13. **Links**

Our Site and Services may contain links to other websites or allow others to send you such links. A link to a third party’s website does not mean that we endorse it or that we are affiliated with it. We do not exercise control over third-party websites and are not responsible for their practices. You access such third-party websites or content at your own risk. You should always read the privacy policy of a third-party website before providing any information to the website.

14. **Children’s Privacy**

The Site and Services are intended for users who are 18 years old or older. We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 13. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received Personal Information from a child under the age of 13, we will delete such information from our records.

15. **Processing in the United States**

Please be aware that your Personal Information and communications may be transferred to and maintained on servers or databases located outside your state, province, or country. If you are located outside of the United States, please be advised that we process and store all information in the United States. The laws in the United States may not be as protective of your privacy as those in your location. Personal information processed and stored in another country may be subject to disclosure or access requests by the governments, courts or law enforcement or regulatory agencies in that country according to its laws. By using the Site or Services, you are agreeing to the collection, use, transfer, and disclosure of your Personal Information and communications will be governed by the applicable laws in the United States. If you have any questions regarding international data transfers, you may contact us using the contact information we provide below.

16. **Notice to Residents of Canada**

If you are a resident of Canada, you may have certain privacy rights under Canadian privacy law.

You have a right to request access to your personal information and to request a correction to it if you believe it is inaccurate. If you would like to have access to the personal information we have about you, or if you would like to have it corrected, please contact us using the contact information provided on the Site. Please note that in some cases, we may not be able to allow you to access certain personal information in certain circumstances, for example if it contains personal information of other persons, or for legal reasons.

To help protect against fraudulent requests for access to your personal information, we may ask you for information to allow us to confirm that the person making the request is you or is authorized to access your information before granting access. For example, we may require you to verify your identity before you access your personal information.

Subject to limitations under the law, you may also withdraw your consent to our processing of your personal information. Please note that this does not affect the lawfulness of processing based on consent before it is withdrawal. Please note that if you seek to withdraw consent to processing of personal data that is necessary for us to provide you with goods or services, we may no longer be able to provide such goods or services to you.

17. **Privacy Policy Changes**

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we decide to change this Privacy Policy, we will inform you by posting the revised Privacy Policy on the Site. Those changes will go into effect on the “Revised” date shown in the revised Privacy Policy. By continuing to use the Site or Services, you are consenting to the revised Privacy Policy.

18. **Contact Us**

If you have any questions or concerns, or would like to submit a complaint to us, you may contact us at the contact information available on the Site.

**Please print a copy of this privacy policy for you records and please check the Site frequently for any changes.**

[\[email protected\]](https://charactersforhire.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) [](https://twitter.com/characters4hire "Twitter") [](https://www.yelp.com/biz/characters-for-hire-new-york-2?osq=characters+for+hire "Yelp") [](https://www.instagram.com/charactersforhire/ "Instagram")

DISCLAIMER: ALL COSTUMED CHARACTERS ARE GENERIC/INSPIRED AND ARE NOT AFFILIATED, LICENSED OR ASSOCIATED WITH ANY CORPORATION OR TRADEMARK. It is not our intention to violate any copyright laws. The characters that we offer are NOT name brand copyrighted characters, and Characters for Hire, LLC. costumed characters are named of our own creation. Any resemblance to nationally known copyrighted characters is strictly coincidental. Should you have the need for a licensed, copyrighted mascot or character at your event, we encourage you to contact the company/copyright holders for your specific targeted character. If you have any questions regarding this issue, we encourage you to contact us. We DO NOT offer nor do we present any licensed and/or copyrighted characters.

2024 Copyright - Characters for Hire, LLC

You cannot copy content of this page
